A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Scientific Staff Collected Reprints FA1119
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Scientific Staff Collected Reprints
1884-1983
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
FA1119
11.79 Cubic Feet 9 standard record storage boxes
Arrangement
Alphabetical
Scope and Contents
Contains articles authored or co-authored by Scientific staff and faculty of the Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research/Rockefeller University. Some articles compiled in this collection were authored by others in the field, and subsequently collected by RU Faculty.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 450.2
- Abernethy, T. J. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Agosta, William C. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Ahrens, Edward H., 1948-1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Allfrey, V., 1952-1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Amano, T., 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Amoss, H. L. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Avery, Oswald T (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Babcock, James W. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Baker, Lilian E., 1926-1929 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Bardin, C. Wayne, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Bearn, A. G., 1951-1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Bergmann, Max, 1939-1942 (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
- Berry, Charles M., 1944 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Blake, John B. (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Blinks, L., 1930-1936 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Brink, Frank, 1939-1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Bronk, Detlev W. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Brown, Wade H. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Burrows, Montrose T., 1911 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Burt, Anges S., 1943 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Campbell, Richard D., 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 47, 77)
- Carrel, Alexis, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Choppin, P. W., 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Choppin, P. W., 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Clark, Harry (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Cohn, Alfred E. (Box 1, Folder 16-24)
- Cohn, Alfred E. (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
- Craig, Lyman C., 1938 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Cranefiled, Paul (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Csapo, A., 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Diacumakos, Elaine, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Dobzhansky, T., 1959-1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Dole, Vincent, 1943-1961 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
- Dubos, Rene, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Duran-Reynals, F., 1928-1939 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Dziewiatkowski, D., 1945-1957 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Edelman, Gerald M., 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Edelman, Gerald M., 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Elek, Adalbert, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Fasoli, Angelo (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Fenn, W. O. (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Flexner, Simon (Box 2, Folder 15-18)
- Frenster, John H. (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Fruton, Joseph S. and Lavin, G. I., 1939 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Gallego, Antonio, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Ganoza, M. Clelia, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Gasser, Herbert S., 1936-1960 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Grafstein, Bernice, 1967, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 16, 74, 78)
- Green, Lorna, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Gregory, John D., 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Grover, N. B., 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 64-65, 72)
- Grundfest, H., 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Haas, Hermann J., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Hanafusa, Hidesaburo (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Hartline, H. K., 1925-1968 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Harvey, Ethel Browne, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Hastings, A. Baird, 1919-1926 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Hirsch, James G., 1951-1964 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Hirsch, James G., 1951-1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Hirsch, Jules, 1955-1959 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Hodgkin, A. L., 1938 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Horiuchi, Kensuke and Moses, Phyllis B., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Hursh, John B., 1940 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Hursh, John B., 1939 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Kavanau, J. Lee, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Keegan, J. J. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kemp, Norman E., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Kunkel, Henry G., 1946-1958 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
- Kreutzberg, G. W., 1968 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Landsteiner, Karl (Box 3, Folder 6-10)
- Lehmann, Jorgen Erik, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Levene, P. A. T. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Linden, Ian, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 75)
- Lippman, Fritz, 1933-1970 (Box 3, Folder 12-17)
- Lippman, Fritz, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Lloyd, David P. C., 1937-1957 (Box 3, Folder 18-19)
- Lloyd, David P. C., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Longsworth, Lewis (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Lord Adrian, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Lorente de No, R., 1932-1957 (Box 4, Folder 2-5)
- Lorente de No, R., 1938-1964 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Luck, J. L., 1964-1981 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Lynch, Clara, 1921-1954 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- McEwen, Bruce S. and Grafstein, Bernice, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- McEwen, Bruce, 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 48-49)
- McMaster, Philip D. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Maramorosch, Karl (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Matolsky, A. G., 1958 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Merrifield, R. Bruce, 1947-1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Michaelis, Lenor (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Michaelis, Lenor (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Michaelis, Lenor; Rous, P.; Pearce, L. (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Mirsky, A. E. (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Model, Peter, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Moore, Stanford, 1940-1974 (Box 4, Folder 11-15)
- Moscona, A., 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Murray, Marion (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Northrup, John N., 1935 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Northrup, John N., 1915-1952 (Box 4, Folder 16-20)
- Oliver, Jean (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Olitsky, Peter (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Opie, E. L. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Orrego, Fernando, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Orcutt, M. L. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Palade, G. E., 1951-1954 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Palay, Sanford L., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Peachey, Lee D. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Pierce, Cynthia, 1947-1957 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Pillai, P. A., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- Poole, Brian, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Porter, Keith, 1945-1947 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Prudden, T. M., 1921 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Rabus, Hartmut, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 76)
- Ratliff, F., 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Renshaw, Birdsey, 1940-1942 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Rhea, Robert P., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Rhoads, C. P. (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Riordan, John, 1931-1976 (Box 5, Folder 11-13)
- Rizack, Martin, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Robbins, E., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Robbins, N., 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Robertson, Oswald (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Rous, Peyton, 1919-1938 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Rosenberg, Murray D., 1960-1965 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Rudomin, P. Z. (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Rudzinski, M., 1954-1958 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Runnstrom, John, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Schaedler, Russell W., 1955-1957 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Scharrer, Berta, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Scharrer, Ernst, 1939-1946 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Schneider, Howard, 1936-1959 (Box 5, Folder 20-21)
- Schonheyder, Fritz, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Schope, Richard, 1926-1961 (Box 5, Folder 22-24)
- Scott, B. I. H., 1963 (Box 9, Folder 71)
- Siekevitz, P., 1970 October 16 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Smadel, Joseph E. (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Smith, Theobald, 1884-1895 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Smith, Theobald, 1895-1934 (Box 6, Folder 1-14)
- Smith, Theobald, 1884-1934 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
- Stoll, Norman (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
- Tamm, I., 1970 October 18 (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
- Tatum, E. L., 1953-1976 (Box 7, Folder 8-12)
- Taylor, A. Cecil, 1960-1965; There is no Box 9, Folder 43. (Box 9, Folder 44-45)
- Taylor, Herbert (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Therman, Per Olof, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Toennies, Jan F., 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Trager, William, 1934-1958 (Box 7, Folder 14-15, Box 8, Folder 1)
- Vanable, J. W., Jr., 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 70)
- Vidali, Giorgio, 1964-1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Webster, Leslie T., 1920-1946 (Box 8, Folder 3-8)
- Zinder, Norton, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Webster, Leslie T., 1920-1946 (Box 8, Folder 1-5)
- Weiss, Paul, 1944-1961 (Box 8, Folder 9-11)
- Weiss, Paul, 1930-1977 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Wong, Tai Wai, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- World War I (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
- Zinder, Norton, 1954-1958 (Box 8, Folder 14)